<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SecureIQLab</title>
    <link>https://secureiqlab.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SecureIQLab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 21:28:07 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://secureiqlab.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://secureiqlab.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 21:28:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://secureiqlab.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Methodology Lifecycle</title>
      <link>https://secureiqlab.github.io/methodology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 21:27:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://secureiqlab.github.io/methodology/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://secureiqlab.github.io/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 21:27:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://secureiqlab.github.io/services/</guid>
      <description>Custom cybersecurity solution validation Validation services tailored to what enterprises want to highlight and focus on. Unlike other testing/ research / analyst firms, our evaluations are built on data gathered hands-on in a lab. Our Validation metrics can be either be based out of a single product/solution or competitive; evaluating a single product or solution or offering, or multiple offerings spread across several competitors.
SecureIQLab engineers and analysts work with enterprises and security vendors to develop a test plan specific to their business requirements and use-cases, then carry out the evaluation either in our lab facility in Austin, TX or our partner lab site, or any combination thereof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://secureiqlab.github.io/aboutus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 21:27:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://secureiqlab.github.io/aboutus/</guid>
      <description>SecureIQLab is a US-based independent, third-party cybersecurity solution validation and advisory service provider. SecureIQLab specializes in assessing and validating a multitude of cyber threat-facing cybersecurity solutions that aim to defend enterprise IT systems and applications from attacks through prevention, detection and effective response.
The enterprise use-case validation criteria and models were developed over years of experience working with several Analyst and testing firms, Fortune-500 enterprises and multiple security technology/solution vendors. These enterprise specific use-case metrics helps bridge the “Cyber-Gap” exposure for them by reducing their operational risk through effective validation of their security controls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Us ?</title>
      <link>https://secureiqlab.github.io/whyus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 21:27:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://secureiqlab.github.io/whyus/</guid>
      <description> Dependability in the face of Insecurity  Major Analyst firm&amp;rsquo;s plagued by subjective opinion and no empirical data Major testing organizations DO NOT FOCUS on Enterprise specific use-cases that matter – Test Metrics with NO Operational Risk Metrics factored in. Key enterprise Security solutions/technology ecosystem &amp;lsquo;NOT&amp;rsquo; looked into. No Relevant Mapping of Enterprise &amp;ldquo;Use-cases&amp;rdquo; to Analyst/testing firms &amp;ldquo;Test-cases&amp;rdquo;.  People  25+ of combined security experience 15+ years of combined 3rd Party market/technology/solution validation experience 10+ years of combined product and technology strategy from “Conception” to “Launch” Stages  Market Know-how  Market Overview Total Addressable Market Value, Growth rate along with 1,3,5 year projections Market Direction Solution Growth Cycle Enterprise Adoption Small-to-Medium-Large-Very Large Enterprise Exposure Enterprise Value metrics derived from Fortune-500 companies Cybersecurity Vendor Landscape Enterprise use cases vs security vendor product features/capabilities  Technology Expertise  Methodology, validation use-case and technology based test case creation End-to-end technology stack know how IT vs SysOps vs DevOps centric focus CISO/CIO focused briefs  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>